Simone Hassan

Email: simoneubax@gmail.com | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/simonehassan/ |

Place: Bournemouth

A fully certified Front End Developer after studying a course by Learning People. I'm a diligent and enthusiastic person who is skilled in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript plus modern libraries and frameworks. Excels at creating pixel-perfect designs and working with cross-browser compatibility issues. Programming to deliver immersive and engaging user experience through efficient website development, version control and testing, proactive feature optimization, and relentless debugging, implement visually appealing and functional design elements. After learning the API course, I gained new skills to create a working piece of software that is easy to communicate with the user and help the company achieve its software development goals.

Core Skills

Microsoft Offices	HTML5	Bootstrap	JavaScript
Google Doc/Sheets/Slides	CSS3	REACT.js	NODE.js
Github	Tailwind	Git	Responsive Web Design/API

Education

LinkedIn certification - UX Web forms	Oct 2022
LinkedIn certification - Web API	Oct 2022
Development Skillsoft certification – Front End	Nov 2021 – July 2022
Learning People Global ltd. – Front End Developer	Nov 2021 – Present
Regio Opleidingen Centrum, Amsterdam - Social Worker	Sept 2019 - Dec 2019
Knowledge about social issues, psychology, and health care	
Regio Opleidingen Centrum, Amsterdam - Tailor Assistant 2019	Aug 2017 - Jul
Designing, making the patterns and sewing the design	
Regio Opleidingen Centrum, Amsterdam – Tailor	Aug 2015 - Jul 2017
Measure clothing and sewing	
A.G Bell High school, Amsterdam	Aug 2010 - Jul 2015

Projects

Details of my personal projects on my Github: https://github.com/Hawadacirka

Project title: Calculator

Level VMBO BB, equivalent to GCS

Technologies: HTML/CSS/JavaScript/Bootstrap

Brief description: I designed a calculator with pastel colours on the web page. It is like

machine calculator with colourful style.

Project title: Ecommerce Ari

Frameworks/languages: HTML/CSS/JavaScript/Boxicons(Icons)

Brief description: I made a responsive shopping website about essential oils.

Project title: Sounds boxes

Frameworks/languages: HTML/CSS/JavaScript

Brief description: A melody can be created by clicking several genres of the music at once.

Project title: Pairs Game

Frameworks/languages: HTML/CSS/JavaScript/Bootstrap

Brief description: You should find the same pairing cards with limited chances.

Project title: Blackjack

Frameworks/languages: HTML/CSS/JavaScript/Bootstrap

Brief description: Playing blackjack is similar to maths, in that both involve solving problems.

Work Experience

NHS UHD in Bournemouth as Housekeeping Assistant

May 2021 – Present

• My duties include – cleaning in general wards, toilets, bathrooms, kitchen, corridors.

NHS St. Ann Hospital in Poole as Domestic Assistant

Jan 2021 – May 2021

• My duties include – cleaning in covid-19 areas, toilets, bathrooms, living rooms, general mental wards.

The Bristowe in Bournemouth as a Kitchen Assistant

Feb 2020 - Oct 2020

• My duties include waitressing, washing up and cleaning the kitchen.

Hotel 2 Stay in Amsterdam as a Housekeeper

Jul - Aug 2017

- Summer job
- Duties included Cleaning rooms and getting them ready for the next guests.

Rodi Media Newspaper Delivery in Hoorn

Jun 2011 - Nov 2013

• I had to deliver newspapers every weekend to people's houses.

Interests

- Practising React.js to make better responsive web designs
- Reading articles related HTML/CSS/Tailwind/React.js/Javascript
- Walking
- Yoga